by RentAnAdviser.com
93 million miles from the sun
People get ready‚ get ready
′Cause here it comes It is a light
A beautiful light
Over the horizon in to your eyes
Oh‚ my‚ my
How beautiful
Oh my beautiful mother
She told me
Son in life You are gona go far
If you do it right
You′ll love where you are
Just know that wherever you go
You can always come home
240 thousand miles from the moon
You have come a long
way to belong here
To share this view of the night
A glorious night
Over the horizon is another bright sky
Oh‚ my‚ my
How beautiful
Oh my irrefutable father
He told me
Son sometimes it may seem dark
But the absence of the light
is a necessary part
Just know‚ that You are never alone
You can always come back home
Oh oh oh
You can always come back
Every road is a slippery slope
There is always a hand that
you can hold on to
Looking deeper through the telescope
You can see that your
homes inside of you
Just know‚ that wherever you go
No You are never alone
You will always get back home
93 million miles from the sun
People get ready‚ get ready
′Cause here it comes It is a light
A beautiful light
Over the horizon in to our eyes
by RentAnAdviser.com